<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on bkjha.com</title>
    <link>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on bkjha.com</description>
    <image>
      <title>bkjha.com</title>
      <url>https://www.bkjha.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://www.bkjha.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:57:39 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.bkjha.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>back again</title>
      <link>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:57:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/back-again/</guid>
      <description>hi, aadab, namaskar, sat sri akal, hola
it&amp;rsquo;s been more than 2 and half year since i last posted something here. i&amp;rsquo;ll use this post as an opportunity to go back in time.
it&amp;rsquo;s been so long that i even forgot how to use Hugo(the framework used for this blog). in between, the domain had expired. thankfully no one claimed it for more than an year - perks of choosing a not so fancy domain name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix: E: Unmet dependencies. and E: Sub-process /usr/bin/dpkg returned an error code (1)</title>
      <link>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/fix-unmet-dependencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 15:14:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/fix-unmet-dependencies/</guid>
      <description>Hi there &amp;#x1f44b;
If you&amp;rsquo;re trying to install/update/remove/fix a debian package and getting the error mentioned in title, and none of the following commands are working,
sudo apt-get remove sudo apt-get install sudo apt-get purge sudo apt-get autoremove sudo apt-get autoclean sudo apt-get install -f you&amp;rsquo;re at the right place.
You&amp;rsquo;ll face this error if you&amp;rsquo;ve terminated the installation process of a software package. You may&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten, when and why did you terminate the installation, but that&amp;rsquo;s not an issue, you&amp;rsquo;ll still be able to fix this issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use rclone with OneDrive(Business plan) without Business API access</title>
      <link>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/rclone-onedrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 10:16:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/rclone-onedrive/</guid>
      <description>Hi there &amp;#x1f44b;
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you have to share a report that you&amp;rsquo;re generating programmatically with a consultant in your company every week. Your general approach might be to upload it to your organization&amp;rsquo;s document/file storage platform(e.g OneDrive) and share it. If you&amp;rsquo;ve to do this multiple times, it&amp;rsquo;s boring to perform the same steps over and over again!
What about automating this process? As soon as your report is generated you can run a command that will copy your file present in local to OneDrive server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first blog</title>
      <link>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 21:11:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bkjha.com/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>Hi there &amp;#x1f44b;
Finally, I&amp;rsquo;m done with the setup of my blog. The purpose of this blog will be to share the
&amp;#x1f4ac; Concepts that I keep learning in a simple language &amp;#x1f4da; Books that I read and many other things, that I&amp;rsquo;m also not sure about. Let&amp;rsquo;s hope this blogging spirit continues forever! &amp;#x1f60e;
Have fun, Keep hacking!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
